Asian Painting Photograph Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- 7027 photographs.
  - Ming Dynasty., 2312 (Box 35)
    - Known artists., 2173 (Box 36)
      - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 187 (Box 36)
        - Wu I-Hsien., 1 (Box 38)
        - Wu Jo-Chu., 1 (Box 38)
        - Wu Ling., 2 (Box 38)
        - Wu Shih-En, XVI C., 1 (Box 38)
        - Wu Wei-Yeh, active 1645., 1 (Box 38)
        - Yang Lung-Yu., 1 (Box 38)
        - Yang Wen-Ts'ung, 1597-1645., 2 (Box 38)
        - Yao Kung-Shou., 1 (Box 38)
        - Yao Te-Hou., 1 (Box 38)
        - Yao Tun Tung., 1 (Box 38)
        - Yeh-Chou., 1 (Box 38)
        - Yeh Kuang, XVI C., 1 (Box 38)
        - Yin Hung, XVI C., 2 (Box 38)
        - Ying, Lan, c.1585-1665., 1 (Box 38)
        - Yu Jen., 1 (Box 38)
        - Yu Tseng., 1 (Box 38)
        - Yuan Shang-T'ung, 1570-1661., 1 (Box 38)
      - Individual artists, A-Z., 1986 (Box 38)
        For Ch'uan Ch'i, see: Pa-Ta Shan-Jen.
        - Chang Feng, active c.1645-1670., 7 (Box 38)
        - Chang Fu., 9 (Box 38)
        - Chang Hung, 1580-after 1660., 9 (Box 38)
        - Chang Lu, 1464-1538., 14 (Box 39)
        - Chao Tso, active c.1610-1630., 7 (Box 39)
        - Ch'en Kua, active c.1550-1554., 11 (Box 39)
        - Ch'en Hsien-Chang., 4 (Box 39)
        - Ch'en Hung-Shou, 1599-1652., 54 (Box 39)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 6 (Box 39)
          - Taichung., 40 (Box 39)
            - Miscellaneous works., 13 (Box 39)
            - Assorted Paintings, album., 8 (Box 39)
            - Sixteen Scenes from a Hermit's Life., 19 (Box 39)
          - Washington D. C., 8 (Box 39)
        - Ch'en Ju-Yen, active 1340-1380., 5 (Box 39)
        - Ch'en Shun, 1483-1544., 27 (Box 40)
        - Ch'en Yueh., 4 (Box 40)
        - Ch'eng Chia-Sui, 1565-1643., 11 (Box 40)
        - Cheng Chung, active c.1565-1630., 3 (Box 40)
        - Cheng Wen-Lin, XVI C., 5 (Box 40)
        - Chiang Sung, XVI C., 10 (Box 40)
        - Ch'ien Ku, 1508-after 1574., 43 (Box 40)
        - Ch'iu Ying, c.1510-1552., 93 (Box 41)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 12 (Box 41)
          - Kansas City., 12 (Box 41)
          - Taichung., 48 (Box 41)
            - Miscellaneous works., 23 (Box 41)
            - The Book of Filial Piety, with Wen Ching-Ming., 6 (Box 41)
            - Copy of Six Scenes from Sung and Yuan, album., 6 (Box 41)
            - Spring Dawn in the Han Palace, handscroll., 13 (Box 41)
          - Washington D. C., 21 (Box 41)
        - Chou Ch'en, active 1500-1535., 37 (Box 42)
        - Chou Chih-Mien, active c.1580-1610., 10 (Box 42)
        - Chou Lung., 6 (Box 42)
        - Chou T'ien-Ch'iu, 1514-1595., 5 (Box 42)
        - Chuh Chieh., 6 (Box 42)
        - Chu Tuan, active c.1505-1525., 7 (Box 42)
        - Hsia Ch'ang, 1388-1470., 28 (Box 42)
        - Hsiang Sheng-Mo, 1597-1658., 33 (Box 43)
        - Hsiang Yuan-Pien, 1525-1590., 7 (Box 43)
        - Hsieh Shih-Ch'en, 1487- after 1567., 29 (Box 43)
        - Hsu Pen, 1345-1397., 15 (Box 43)
        - Hsu Wei, 1520-1593., 24 (Box 43)
        - Hsuan-Tsung, 1398-1435., 12 (Box 44)
        - Ku Cheng-I, active c.1580., 4 (Box 44)
        - Kuan Ssu, active c.1590-1630., 4 (Box 44)
        - Kuo Hsu, 1456-1526., 6 (Box 44)
        - Lan Ying, 1585- after 1664., 61 (Box 44)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 26 (Box 44)
          - Seattle., 7 (Box 44)
          - Taichung., 28 (Box 44)
            - Miscellaneous works., 1 (Box 44)
            - After Old Masters, album., 5 (Box 44)
            - Birds and Flowers, album., 7 (Box 44)
            - Landscapes after the Old Masters, album., 8 (Box 44)
            - Landscapes and Drawings from Life after the Old Masters, album., 7 (Box 44)
        - Li Chu., 11 (Box 44)
        - Li Liu-Fang, 1575-1629., 7 (Box 45)
        - Li Shao-Ch'i., 12 (Box 45)
        - Li Shih-Ta, active c.1573-1619., 3 (Box 45)
        - Li Tsung-Mo., 7 (Box 45)
        - Lin Liang, active c.1485-1505., 16 (Box 45)
        - Liu Chueh, 1410-1472., 4 (Box 45)
        - Liu Chung-Hsien., 3 (Box 45)
        - Lu Chi, active 1484-1505., 29 (Box 45)
        - Lu Chih, 1495-1576., 65 (Box 46)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 7 (Box 46)
          - Taichung., 58 (Box 46)
            - Miscellaneous works., 16 (Box 46)
            - Calligraphy and Painting, hand scroll., 15 (Box 46)
            - Combined Painting and Calligraphy, album., 6 (Box 46)
            - Dragon Spring, hand scroll., 5 (Box 46)
            - Endless Spring in the Immortals' Garden, hand scroll., 6 (Box 46)
            - Paintings from Life, album., 6 (Box 46)
            - The Thatched Hall of Lien-Ch'uan, hand scroll., 4 (Box 46)
        - Lu Shih-Tao, c.1510-1570., 3 (Box 46)
        - Lu Yuan., 8 (Box 46)
        - Pien Wen-Chin, active 1413-1435., 11 (Box 46)
        - Pien Wen-Yu., 19 (Box 46)
        - Shang Hsi, active c.1430-1440., 3 (Box 47)
        - Shao Mi, active c. 1620-1660., 13 (Box 47)
        - Shen Chou, 1427-1509., 231 (Box 47)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 85 (Box 47)
          - Wango H. C. Weng Collection., 22 (Box 47)
          - Taichung., 124 (Box 47)
            - Miscellaneous works., 34 (Box 48)
            - Collection of Views of Wu, album., 8 (Box 48)
            - Falling Flowers, hand scroll., 9 (Box 48)
            - Landscape, hand scroll., 17 (Box 48)
            - Landscapes, signed, album., 11 (Box 48)
            - Landscapes in the Spirit of Ni Tsan, album., 10 (Box 48)
            - Paintings of the Essence, album., 15 (Box 48)
            - Studies of Flowers and Animals, album., 19 (Box 49)
        - Shen Shih-Ch'ung, active c.1611-1640., 10 (Box 49)
        - Shen-Tu, Monk, active c.1650., 4 (Box 49)
        - Sheng Mao-Yeh, c.1625-1640., 16 (Box 49)
        - Shih Jui, c. 1424-1435., 8 (Box 49)
        - Sun K'o-Hung, 1532-1610., 31 (Box 49)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 1 (Box 49)
          - Taichung., 30 (Box 49)
        - Sun Lung., 13 (Box 50)
        - Tai Chin, 1388-1462., 48 (Box 50)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 15 (Box 50)
          - Taichung., 13 (Box 50)
          - Washington D. C., 20 (Box 50)
        - T'ang Yin, 1470-1524., 130 (Box 50)
          - Miscellaneous works., 65 (Box 51)
          - Dreaming of Being an Immortal in the Thatched House., 10 (Box 51)
          - Gathering Lotus Roots, with Wen P'eng, hand scroll., 6 (Box 51)
          - Landscapes and Figures, album., 10 (Box 51)
          - Mountain Dwelling, hand scroll., 8 (Box 51)
          - Parting at Chin-ch'ang, hand scroll., 6 (Box 51)
          - Reciting Poetry in an Autumn Villa, hand scroll., 4 (Box 51)
          - The Scholars, hand scroll., 6 (Box 52)
          - Secluded Fishermen on an Autumn River., 11 (Box 52)
          - Watching the Ploughing, hand scroll., 4 (Box 52)
        - T'ao Ch'eng, active c.1480-1532., 6 (Box 52)
        - Ting Yun-P'eng, 1584-1618., 17 (Box 52)
        - Ting Yun-T'u., 9 (Box 52)
        - Tsou Chih-Lin, active early XVII C., 17 (Box 52)
        - Tsou Heng, active XV C., 13 (Box 52)
        - Ts'ui Tzu-Chung, c.1595-1644., 4 (Box 52)
        - Tu Chin, active 1465-1487., 6 (Box 52)
        - Tu Ch'iung, 1396-1474., 5 (Box 52)
        - Tung Ch'i-Ch'ang, 1555-1636., 146 (Box 52)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 23 (Box 53)
          - Boston., 18 (Box 53)
          - New York., 58 (Box 53)
            - Miscellaneous works., 5 (Box 53)
            - Landscape Album after Old Masters., 53 (Box 53)
          - Taichung., 57 (Box 54)
            - Miscellaneous works., 16 (Box 54)
            - Calligraphy and Painting, album., 20 (Box 54)
            - Landscapes, album., 6 (Box 54)
            - Misty Rivers and Piled-Up Peaks, hand scroll., 4 (Box 54)
            - The Thousand Cliffs and Ten Thousand Valleys., 6 (Box 54)
            - White Clouds and Red Trees, hand scroll., 5 (Box 54)
        - Wan Shou-Ch'i, 1603-1652., 9 (Box 54)
        - Wang E., 6 (Box 54)
        - Wang Fu, 1362-1416., 41 (Box 54)
        - Wang Ku-Hsiang, 1501-1568., 9 (Box 55)
        - Wang Li, 1332-after 1383., 13 (Box 55)
        - Wang Wen, 1497-1576., 7 (Box 55)
        - Wen Cheng-Ming, 1470-1559., 206 (Box 55)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 45 (Box 55)
            - Miscellaneous works., 26 (Box 55)
            - The Red Cliff., 10 (Box 55)
            - Summer Retreat in the Eastern Grove., 9 (Box 55)
          - Princeton., 17 (Box 55)
          - Taichung., 144 (Box 55)
            - Miscellaneous works., 59 (Box 56)
            - Bamboo Paintings, album., 6 (Box 56)
            - Copy of and Illustration to 'Diamond Sutra', with Ch'iu Ying., 4 (Box 56)
            - Elegant Pleasures of Groves and Springs, hand scroll., 8 (Box 56)
            - Flowers, album., 9 (Box 56)
            - I-ch'uan, hand scroll., 7 (Box 56)
            - Imitating Chao Po-su's 'Red Cliff', hand scroll., 12 (Box 56)
            - Lofty Spirits in a Lonely Ravine, hanging scroll., 6 (Box 56)
            - Snow on the Mountain Passes, hand scroll., 13 (Box 57)
            - Snowy Mountain, hand scroll., 8 (Box 57)
            - Springtime Wandering, hand scroll., 4 (Box 57)
            - The Tu-Lo Garden, hand scroll., 8 (Box 57)
        - Wen Chia, 1501-1583., 12 (Box 57)
        - Wen Po-Jen, 1502-1575., 34 (Box 57)
          - Miscellaneous works., 15 (Box 57)
          - Portrait of Yang Chi-Ching, hand scroll., 6 (Box 57)
          - Spring Dawn at Tan-t'ai, hand scroll., 5 (Box 57)
          - Ten Views of Suchou, album., 8 (Box 57)
        - Wu Pin, active c.1568-1621., 46 (Box 58)
          - Miscellaneous works., 17 (Box 58)
          - Eighteen Lohans, hand scroll., 5 (Box 58)
          - Diversion of the Twelve Months, hand scroll., 12 (Box 58)
          - Record of the Year's Holidays, album., 12 (Box 58)
        - Wu Wei, 1458-1508., 22 (Box 58)
        - Yao Shou, 1423-1495., 28 (Box 58)
        - Yen Tsung., 4 (Box 58)
        - Yu Ch'iu, active c.1570-1590., 10 (Box 58)
  - Ch'ing Dynasty., 1468 (Box 59)
    - Unknown artists., 31 (Box 59)
    - Chou Liang-Kung album., 19 (Box 59)
    - Known artists., 1418 (Box 59)
      - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 112 (Box 59)
        - Ai Ch'i-Meng, 1708-1780., 1 (Box 59)
        - Chang Chao, XVIII C., 1 (Box 59)
        - Chang Ch'eng-Lung., 1 (Box 59)
        - Chang Dai-Ch'ien, 1899-1983., 1 (Box 59)
        - Chang Jo-Ai, 1713-1746., 1 (Box 59)
        - Chang Keng, 1685-1760., 1 (Box 59)
        - Chang Ku., 1 (Box 59)
        - Chang P'eng-Ch'ung, 1688-1745., 1 (Box 59)
        - Chang Tsung-Ts'ang, 1686-1756., 1 (Box 59)
        - Chang Yu, 1734-1803., 1 (Box 59)
        - Chao Chih-Ch'ien, 1829-1884., 4 (Box 59)
        - Ch'ao-K'uei, c.1620-c.1700., 1 (Box 59)
        - Ch'en Shu, 1660-1736., 2 (Box 59)
        - Ch'en Yueh., 1 (Box 59)
        - Cheng Hsieh, 1693-1765., 2 (Box 59)
        - Cheng Sui, 1605-1691., 1 (Box 59)
        - Cheng Sung., 1 (Box 59)
        - Ch'eng Ting-Lu, 1797-1859., 1 (Box 59)
        - Chiang Chu., 1 (Box 59)
        - Chiao Ping-Chen., 1 (Box 59)
        - Ch'ien Feng, 1740-c.1795., 2 (Box 59)
        - Ch'ien-Lung, 1711-1799., 2 (Box 59)
        - Ch'ien Tsai, 1708-1793., 1 (Box 59)
        - Ch'ien Tu, 1763-1844., 1 (Box 59)
        - Ch'ien Wei-Ch'eng, 1720-1772., 3 (Box 59)
        - Chin T'ing-Piao, active c.1720-1760., 2 (Box 59)
        - Chin Tzu-T'ai., 1 (Box 59)
        - Ching-Jui., 2 (Box 59)
        - Chou Hsun, 1649-1729., 1 (Box 59)
        - Chu Sheng, 1618-after 1690., 3 (Box 59)
        - Fa Jo-Chen, 1613-1696., 2 (Box 60)
        - Fu-Mei, 1628-1682., 1 (Box 60)
        - Ho I, active c.1700., 1 (Box 60)
        - Hsi Kang, 1746-1803., 2 (Box 60)
        - Hsiao Ch'en, active c.1680-1710., 2 (Box 60)
        - Hsu-Ku, 1824-1895., 4 (Box 60)
        - Huang Ying-Shen, active c.1644-1661., 1 (Box 60)
        - Hung Wu, active c.1736-1795., 2 (Box 60)
        - Jen Po-Nien, 1840-1896., 1 (Box 60)
        - Kai Ch'i, 1774-1829., 2 (Box 60)
        - Ku Chien-Lung, 1606-after 1686., 1 (Box 60)
        - Ku Ta-Shen, active c.1650-1675., 1 (Box 60)
        - Kuo Tung-Chou, XX C., 1 (Box 60)
        - Li Shan, 1711-1762., 4 (Box 60)
        - Li Yu, 1611-., 1 (Box 60)
        - Lo Mu, 1622-after 1706., 1 (Box 60)
        - Lu Hsueh, c.1750., 1 (Box 60)
        - Lu Tai-Yu., 1 (Box 60)
        - Ma Ch'uan., 1 (Box 60)
        - Niu Shih-Hui., 1 (Box 60)
        - P'an Kung-Shou, 1741-1794., 1 (Box 60)
        - Shang-Kuan Chou., 1 (Box 60)
        - Shih-Tsu, emperor, 1638-1661., 1 (Box 60)
        - Shu-Jui., 2 (Box 60)
        - Su Hsu-Ku, 1821-1850., 1 (Box 60)
        - Ta Chung-Kuang, 1623-1692., 1 (Box 60)
        - T'ang Tai, active c.1708-1750., 1 (Box 60)
        - Ts'ai Chia, 1680-1760., 2 (Box 60)
        - Ts'ai Han (Ts'ai Nu-Lo), 1647-after 1691., 1 (Box 60)
        - Tsou Che, 1636-1708., 2 (Box 60)
        - Tsou I-Kuei, 1686-1772., 1 (Box 60)
        - Tung Kao, 1740-1818., 1 (Box 60)
        - Tung T'ing., 1 (Box 60)
        - Tzu Hsi, Empress Dowager, c.1886, 1 (Box 60)
        - Wang Liang-Ch'en., 2 (Box 60)
        - Wang Shih-I., 1 (Box 60)
        - Wang Shih-Shen, active c.1730-1750., 4 (Box 60)
        - Wang Shu-Ch'i., 1 (Box 60)
        - Wang Su, 1794-1877., 1 (Box 60)
        - Wang Yu (Wang Tung-Chuang), active XVII-XVIII C., 1 (Box 60)
        - Wu Ch'ang-Shih, 1844-1927., 2 (Box 60)
        - Wu Tan, active 1672-after 1708., 1 (Box 60)
        - Wu Wei-Yeh, 1669-1671., 1 (Box 60)
        - Yun Hsi., 1 (Box 60)
        - Yung Jung., 1 (Box 60)
      - Individual artists, A-Z., 1306 (Box 60)
        For Chu Ta, see Pa-Ta-Shan-Jen, Painting, China, Ch'ing.
        For Tao-Chi, see Shih-T'ao, Painting, China, Ch'ing.
        - Cha Chi-Tso, 1601-1677., 23 (Box 60)
        - Cha Shih-Piao, 1615-1698., 12 (Box 60)
        - Ch'en Mei, active 1730-1742., 10 (Box 60)
        - Chiang T'ing-Hsi, 1669-1732., 4 (Box 60)
        - Chin K'u., 10 (Box 61)
        - Chin Nung, 1687-1763., 13 (Box 61)
        - Chuan Chiung-Shen, 1627-1679., 15 (Box 61)
        - Fan Ch'i, active c.1660., 9 (Box 61)
        - Fang Shih-Shu, 1692-1751., 12 (Box 61)
        - Fu Shan, 1607-1684., 3 (Box 61)
        - Hsiao Yun-Ts'ung, 1596-1673., 21 (Box 61)
        - Hsu Yang, active c.1760., 17 (Box 61)
        - Hua Yen, 1682-1756., 10 (Box 61)
        - Huang Hsiang-Chien, 1609-1673., 39 (Box 62)
          - Journey to Find Parents, album., 18 (Box 62)
          - Scenes of Travel, album., 21 (Box 62)
        - Huang Shen, 1687-after 1768., 21 (Box 62)
        - Huang Ting, 1660-1730., 7 (Box 62)
        - Hung-Jen, 1610-1663., 4 (Box 62)
        - Kao Ch'i-P'ei, -1734., 4 (Box 62)
        - Kao Feng-Han, 1683-after 1747., 15 (Box 62)
        - Ku K'uei, XIX C., 8 (Box 62)
        - K'un-Ts'an, 1612-after 1692., 21 (Box 62)
        - Kung Hsien, active c.1655-1689., 42 (Box 63)
        - Lan Shen., 5 (Box 63)
        - Lang Shih-Ning, 1688-1768., 71 (Box 63)
          - Miscellaneous works., 21 (Box 63)
          - An Academic Painting of Raising Silkworms, hand scroll., 24 (Box 63)
          - Four Horses from Afghanistan, hand scroll., 7 (Box 63)
          - The Hundred Horses, hand scroll., 7 (Box 63)
          - Ma-Ch'ang in Battle, hand scroll., 4 (Box 63)
          - Spring Birds and Flowers, album., 8 (Box 63)
        - Leng Mei, XVIII C., 4 (Box 64)
        - Li Shih-Cho, active 1741-c.1765., 9 (Box 64)
        - Liu Yu, active c.1700., 24 (Box 64)
        - Lo P'ing, 1733-1799., 14 (Box 64)
        - Lu Wei, active c.1700., 6 (Box 64)
        - Mei Ch'ing, 1623-1679., 6 (Box 64)
        - Pa-Ta-Shan-Jen, active 1634-1650., 77 (Box 64)
          - Miscellaneous works., 45 (Box 64)
          - Landscape Album., 32 (Box 65)
        - Shih T'ao, 1642-1707., 234 (Box 65)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 58 (Box 65)
            - Miscellaneous works., 51 (Box 65)
            - Ten Thousand Ugly Ink Dots., 7 (Box 65)
          - Boston., 11 (Box 66)
            - Album of 12 Paintings., 11 (Box 66)
          - Cleveland., 14 (Box 66)
            - Miscellaneous works., 5 (Box 66)
            - Reminiscences of Ch'in-Huai River, album., 9 (Box 66)
          - Hong Kong., 34 (Box 66)
          - Kyoto., 9 (Box 66)
          - London., 8 (Box 66)
            - Eight Views of the South., 8 (Box 66)
          - Los Angeles., 8 (Box 66)
            - Album of Landscapes., 8 (Box 66)
          - New York., 40 (Box 66)
            - Miscellaneous works., 20 (Box 66)
            - Scenes of Chin-Ling, album., 13 (Box 67)
            - Portrait of Hung Kai-Hua., 7 (Box 67)
          - Osaka.., 12 (Box 67)
            - Illustration to a Preface to a Poem by Su Tung-P'o., 12 (Box 67)
          - Princeton., 40 (Box 67)
            - Miscellaneous works., 5 (Box 67)
            - Landscape and Flowers., 24 (Box 67)
            - Album of Landscape., 11 (Box 67)
        - Sun Ku., 4 (Box 67)
        - Tai Hsi, 1801-1860., 16 (Box 67)
        - Tai Pen-Hsiao, active 1660-1690., 5 (Box 67)
        - Ting Kuan-P'eng, active c.1745-1765., 23 (Box 67)
        - Tung Pang-Ta, 1699-1769., 5 (Box 68)
        - Wang Ch'en, 1720-1797., 5 (Box 68)
        - Wang Chien, 1598-1677., 23 (Box 68)
        - Wang Hui, 1632-1717., 137 (Box 68)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 52 (Box 68)
          - Taichung., 85 (Box 69)
            - Miscellaneous works., 35 (Box 69)
            - Flowers and Landscaps, album., 13 (Box 69)
            - Imitations of Sung and Yuan Landscapes, album., 7 (Box 69)
            - Imitations of Various Landscape Styles, album., 4 (Box 69)
            - Ink Paintings, album., 6 (Box 69)
            - Landscape, hand scroll., 4 (Box 69)
            - Misty Rain in Summer Mountains, hand scroll., 8 (Box 69)
            - Morning Colors on Mountain Peaks, hand scroll., 4 (Box 69)
            - Streams, Mountains and Village, hand scroll., 4 (Box 69)
        - Wang Shih-Min, 1582-1680., 34 (Box 70)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 13 (Box 70)
          - Taichung., 21 (Box 70)
            - Miscellaneous works., 1 (Box 70)
            - Album after Sung and Yuan Masters., 20 (Box 70)
        - Wang Shu-Ku, 1647-c.1730., 9 (Box 70)
        - Wang Wu, 1632-1690., 8 (Box 70)
        - Wang Yuan-Ch'i, 1642-1715., 73 (Box 70)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 28 (Box 70)
          - Taichung., 45 (Box 70)
            - Miscellaneous works., 14 (Box 70)
            - Landscape, hand scroll., 11 (Box 70)
            - Landscapes, album., 12 (Box 70)
            - Landscapes after Sungand Yuan Artists, album., 8 (Box 70)
        - Wen Tien, 1633-1704., 10 (Box 71)
        - Wu Li, 1632-1718., 23 (Box 71)
        - Yang Chin, 1644-1726., 13 (Box 71)
        - Yao Sung, active c.1700., 9 (Box 71)
        - Yeh Hsin, active c.1650., 8 (Box 71)
        - Yu Chih-Ting, 1647-1705., 6 (Box 71)
        - Yuan Chiang, XVIII C., 5 (Box 71)
        - Yuan Yao, XVIII C., 3 (Box 72)
        - Yun Hsiang, c.1640., 8 (Box 72)
        - Yun Shou-P'ing, 1632-1690., 79 (Box 72)
          - Miscellaneous locations., 31 (Box 72)
          - Taichung., 48 (Box 72)
            - Miscellaneous works., 14 (Box 72)
            - Copies of the Old Masters., 11 (Box 72)
            - Eight Flower Paintings, album., 4 (Box 72)
            - Flower Paintings in Ink, album., 3 (Box 72)
            - Landscapes, album., 9 (Box 72)
            - Sketches, album., 7 (Box 72)
  - XX Century., 129 (Box 72)
    - Unknown artists., 1 (Box 73)
    - Known artists., 128 (Box 73)
      - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 39 (Box 73)
        - Chen Ch'i-K'uan, 1921-., 2 (Box 73)
        - Ch'en Heng-K'o., 1 (Box 73)
        - Chen Jialing, 1937-., 1 (Box 73)
        - Chen Yifei, 1946-., 2 (Box 73)
        - Chiang Kai-shek, Madame., 2 (Box 73)
        - Chin Kung-Po., 1 (Box 73)
        - Fu Baoshi, 1904-1965., 1 (Box 73)
        - Gao Jiangfu, 1879-1951., 1 (Box 73)
        - Gao Qifeng, 1889-1933., 2 (Box 73)
        - Hsu Pei-Hung, 1895-1953., 3 (Box 73)
        - Huang Pin-Hung, 1863-1954., 1 (Box 73)
        - Huang Yung-Yu., 1 (Box 73)
        - Jiang Zhaoshen., 2 (Box 73)
        - Kao Lun, 1879-1951., 1 (Box 73)
        - Kuan Shan-Yueh, 1912-., 1 (Box 73)
        - Li Huasheng, 1944-., 1 (Box 73)
        - Li Keran, 1907-1989., 1 (Box 73)
        - Liu Guosong, 1932-., 2 (Box 73)
        - Pan Tianshou, 1897-1971., 1 (Box 73)
        - P'u C'huan., 2 (Box 73)
        - Ren Yi, 1840-1895., 2 (Box 73)
        - Wang, C. C., 1907-., 3 (Box 73)
        - Wang Chen-Hai of Shanghai., 1 (Box 73)
        - W'ang He Nien., 1 (Box 73)
        - Wang Te-Wei., 1 (Box 73)
        - Wang Yidong, 1955-., 1 (Box 73)
        - Wu Ch'ang-Shih, 1844-1927., 1 (Box 73)
        - Yeh Chien-Yu, 1907-., 1 (Box 73)
      - Individual artists, A-Z., 89 (Box 73)
        - Ch'ang Dai-Ch'ien, 1899-1983., 13 (Box 73)
        - Chang Ta-Ch'ien., 9 (Box 73)
        - Fu Baoshi, 1904-1965., 8 (Box 73)
        - Lin Fengman, 1900-., 10 (Box 74)
        - Qi Baisha, 1863-1957., 32 (Box 74)
        - Shi Lu, 1919-1982., 6 (Box 74)
        - Wu Guanzhong, 1919-., 5 (Box 74)
        - Xu Beihong, 1895-1953., 6 (Box 74)
- Central Asia., 13 (Box 74)
  - Unknown artists., 13 (Box 74)
    - Unknown site., 1 (Box 74)
    - Kucha sites., 6 (Box 74)
    - Miran., 1 (Box 74)
    - Shorchuk., 1 (Box 74)
    - Turfan sites., 4 (Box 74)
- India., 157 (Box 74)
  - Unknown artists., 150 (Box 74–75)
    - Miscellaneous works., 24 (Box 75)
    - Buddhist., 71 (Box 75)
      - Miscellaneous locations., 6 (Box 75)
      - Ajanta., 48 (Box 75)
        Includes a folder of miscellaneous clippings and a folio of prints.
      - Bamiyan valley., 13 (Box 76)
      - Bagh., 4 (Box 76)
    - Moghul., 33 (Box 76)
      - Miscellaneous works., 24 (Box 76)
      - Popular Moghul., 9 (Box 76)
    - Rajput., 22 (Box 76)
  - Known artists., 7 (Box 76)
    - XX Century., 7 (Box 76)
      - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 7 (Box 76)
        - Bendre, N. S., 1 (Box 76)
        - Dave, Shanti., 1 (Box 76)
        - Husain, M. F., 1 (Box 76)
        - Krishna, Devayani., 1 (Box 76)
        - Prabha, B., 1 (Box 76)
        - Sultan Ali, J., 1 (Box 76)
        - Tagore, R., 1861-., 1 (Box 76)
- Japan., 777 (Box 76–77)
  Includes three large folders of miscellaneous clippings.
  - Miscellaneous works., 8 (Box 77)
  - Late Yamato, 552-710., 9 (Box 77)
  - Nara Period, 710-794., 21 (Box 77)
  - Heian Period, 794-1185., 62 (Box 78)
    - Unknown artists., 59 (Box 78)
    - Known artists., 3 (Box 78)
      - Jonin, Enichbo, XIII C., 1 (Box 78)
      - Mitsunaga, Tokiwa, XII C., 2 (Box 78)
      - Takanobu, Fujiwara no, 1142-1205., 1 (Box 78)
  - Kamakura Period, 82 (Box 78)
    - Unknown artists., 67 (Box 78)
      - Miscellaneous locations., 37 (Box 78)
      - Boston., 14 (Box 79)
      - Tokyo., 16 (Box 79)
    - Known artists., 15 (Box 79)
      - Eiga, Takuma, active 1310., 2 (Box 79)
      - En-I, XII C., 1 (Box 79)
      - Nobuzane, Fujiwara, 1176-c.1268., 6 (Box 79)
      - Takakane, Takashina, XIV C., 4 (Box 79)
      - Takanobu, Fujiwara, 1142-1205., 2 (Box 79)
      - Yukihiro, Tosa., 1 (Box 79)
  - Muromachi Period, 1333-1568., 123 (Box 79)
    - Unknown artists., 28 (Box 79)
      - Miscellaneous locations., 11 (Box 79)
      - Kyoto., 8 (Box 79)
      - Shiga., 9 (Box 79)
    - Known artists., 95 (Box 80)
      - Miscellaneous artists, A-Z., 51 (Box 80)
        - Beiai., 1 (Box 80)
        - Bokkei, active XV C., 1 (Box 80)
        - Bompo, Gyokuen, 1344-c.1420., 1 (Box 80)
        - Bunsei, active XV C., 1 (Box 80)
        - Dasoku, -1483., 3 (Box 80)
        - Gakuo, XV C., 1 (Box 80)
        - Geiami, Shingei, 1431-1485., 2 (Box 80)
        - Gukei, Ue, active 1361-1375., 1 (Box 80)
        - Hideyari, Kano, -1557., 1 (Box 80)
        - Kao, XIV C., 4 (Box 80)
        - Masanobu, Kano, 1434-1530., 3 (Box 80)
        - Mincho, Kitsuzan, 1352-1431., 1 (Box 80)